easyfinder.ie 2011-12-31

# Privacy

**EasyFinder Group's Privacy Policy** describes how we handle our clients personal information for our services on the EasyFinder Group websites. 

EasyFinder respects your right to privacy in relation to your advertising with this website. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to outline how we deal with any personal information that we collect from you or that you provide to us while visiting easyfinder.ie. 

Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that EasyFinder does not own or control or to people that EasyFinder does not employ or manage. 

Any data which is provided by you via easyfinder.ie or otherwise will be treated in accordance with the terms of the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2003 and/or such amending or replacement legislation as may be adopted in Ireland from time to time. 

1\. Note about Children: Children (persons under the age of 16) do not submit any personal   
information to us, you may use the website only under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian. 

2\. Information Collection, Usage and Disclosure: When registering with EasyFinder you will be asked to provide certain personal information: 

  * email address, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information, such as credit card or bank account numbers; 
  * other information from your interaction with our sites, services, content and advertising, 
  * including computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the sites, ad data, IP address and standard web log information; 
  * other information, including users IP address and standard web log information. 

Personal data which we collect from you will only be used for the purposes for which it was provided by you.   
EasyFinder will never release your personal information to any third parties without your prior consent. We may disclose user information in response to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. EasyFinder retains the right at all times to contact you in relation to the services provided on this website. We use your personal data to identify you as a customer, to process your advertisement, to verify credit or other charge card details and to deliver relevant information to you in connection with your advertisement. We don't collect or keep your personal data unless it is necessary for the above purposes(s) nor do we keep your personal data for longer than is necessary. 

3\. Cookies: EasyFinder may set and access “cookies" on your computer. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie does not link to any personally identifiable information while on our website. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time.   
You are always free to decline our cookies, if your browser permits, by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. You are always free to ask your browser to indicate when a cookie is being sent. You can also delete cookie files from your computer at your discretion. 

4\. Security: All the information is stored on our servers. We treat data as an asset that must be   
protected and use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. But, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the site. We work very hard to protect your privacy, but we can’t guarantee 100 % security. 

 5\. Links to other websites: Please be aware that where you follow a link to another website from our website, EasyFinder has no control over that other website. Please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and terms of use and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies or for the activities on those websites. 

 6.General: We may update this Privacy Policy at any time and post the amended terms on this site.   
All updates automatically take effect 30 days after they are initially posted on the site. We may also notify you by e-mail. 

If you have questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy and practices, please contact us.
